

ABOUT ME

Experienced web developer with a solid foundation in both front- and back-end development. My creative approach, combined with a positive attitude, enhances my ability to solve complex problems. I'm goal-oriented with a strong drive to further develop my skills as a web developer and have a clear plan to achieve my professional goals.

CONTACT

Cassandraabook@gmail.com +46 706 - 10 83 11 Vasastan, 113 62

LANGUAGE

Swedish English



INTERESTS

- Programming
- Padel
- Exercise
- Social media
- Travel

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS/SASS
- Javascript
- Typescript
- Databases/SQL
- GIT/Github
- API
- PHP
- React
- Photoshop
- Adobe XD

- Adobe Bridge

- Node.js
- Socket.io
- Wordpress
- WooCommerce
- Figma
- Canva
- Notion
- Jira
- Service
- Agile methods
- Tableau

Cassandra Book

WEB DEVELOPER SPECIALIZING IN E-COMMERCE

EDUCATIONS

Web developer specializing in e-commerce

Medieinstitutet | sep 2022 - jun 2024

Degree in Front- and Back-end Development, System Development, Database Technology, Responsive Web Development, E-commerce Systems, System Support, and Third-party Systems.

Events and projects with digital marketing

Södertörns university | jan 2022 - jun 2022

Proficient in project coordination, event experiences, event planning, product concept development, digital marketing, and project management.

WORK EXPERIENCES

Hopen Internship

Front-end developer | oct 2023 - dec 2023

During my LIA at Hopen, I created dynamic web interfaces with React and TypeScript, styled components with SCSS, worked with databases and SQL, and integrated Jira and Notion into the workflow, leveraging Azure for cloud-based solutions.

H&M

Sales advisor | apr 2018 - juni 2022

I handled customer service, merchandise restocking, unpacking of goods, and store fronting on a daily basis, actively took initiative to achieve sales targets.

Floor manager | aug 2018 - aug 2019

In my role as a floor manager, I assisted department managers with daily operations and ensured that work distribution was optimized, with the right staff in the right position. I also monitored sales outcomes and established targets for my team.

BIKBOK

Sales advisor | oct 2015 - apr 2018

As my store manager's right hand, I supervised operational tasks, ensured efficient merchandise management, daily customer service, cashier services, and mentoring of interns. I was responsible for receiving goods and product care, as well as contributing to the store's visual presentation.

Lekia

Sales advisor | feb 2013 - sep 2015

I worked every other weekend during my high school years. My responsibilities included operating the cash register, facing the store, unpacking deliveries, as well as providing customer service.

LINKS

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/cassandra-book-44241344/

https://github.com/Cassandrabook

Portfolio

https://cassandrabooks.com/